Mend your pace sway to the beat
加快步伐，紧随这律动摇摆
Hands up Embrace who you wanna be
高举双手，拥理想自我入怀
We're reaching heights unseen, whoa, whoa-oh ho-oh
我们一起抵达未见之境
Feel the fire deep within
感受着心底火焰
You're the key to where my trust begins
你令我轻启心扉，交托信赖
Join-my-dream it's just the right time, woah-oh-oh ho-oh
加入我的梦境吧，大好时机已来
Leave it all behind
把一切都抛开
All behind
抛在脑后
Get ready now
现在做好准备——
Ready now
准备好——
Rise up into my world
跃升 闯入我的世界
Renew your definition
更新你的定义
World so high let me show
向你展示这里的超乎寻常
And hear my declaration
让你听见我的宣言
No more ties
“从此，再无拘束”
Off the ground and tap your feet
高高跳起，用双脚叩出节拍
Look stars are near when you feel the beat
当你感受到律动，繁星已近在咫尺
We're bound for a greater height, whoa, whoa-oh ho-oh
我们一起触碰更高的天空
Take a leap into the blazing
要向炽燃中飞跃
Don't lose yourself in mundanity
不在凡俗里沉沦
Join-my-dream it is the right time, woah-oh-oh ho-oh
加入我的梦境吧，大好时机已来
Leave it all behind
把一切都抛开
Get ready now
现在做好准备
Sing along
随我一起高唱
Welcome to my world
欢迎来到我的世界
Renew your definition
更新你的定义
World so high let me show
向你展示这里的超乎寻常
And hear my declaration
让你听见我的宣言
No more ties
“从此，再无拘束”
Leave it all behind
把一切都抛开
Welcome to my world
欢迎来到我的世界
Renew your definition
更新你的定义
World so high let me show
向你展示这里的超乎寻常
Now hear my declaration
现在请静静地聆听
Welcome to my world
欢迎来到我的世界
Renew your definition
更新你的定义
World so high we'll show
我们要向世人证明这里的超乎寻常
And go beyond horizon
越过地平线
Side by side
肩并着肩